A Guide to the Joshua Lederberg personal papers, Subject File FA1087
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject File, 1
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Population Growth and Degrad Global Environment (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Prizes (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Resignation Letters (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller University - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Roundtable (held at Rockefeller University), 1986 January 7 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - National Security Controls on International Techology Transfer, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - National Research Council (NRC)-Teleconference Facilities (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Membership, 1983-1989 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Nomination Forms - Membership (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Proceedings (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - DIR (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Sci Rev Award (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Travel Voucher (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - S and T (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Annual Meeting, 1985 April 21-24 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Mariner IV, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Annual Meeting, 1988 April 26 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - EO Biology Workshops, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - National Research Council (NRC) - Exp. Res. Needs for User-Information System Interaction, 1983 October (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 42-43)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) - Life Sciences, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - NASA - Life Sciences Meeting - Presentation and Members List, 1988 November 22-23 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - NASA - Life Sciences Committee (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NASA - Mars (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - NASA - SETI (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NASA - Life Sciences Meeting - Presentation and Members List, 1988 November 22-23 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NASA, 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NASA - Automated Space Station, 1984 March 18-19 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NASA-SSB 1960s - AIBS Rev 1982, 1960s-1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NASA - Workshop on Exobiology, 1982 December (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NASA - Life Sciences Division - Subcommittee Meeting, 1989 June 19-20 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - NASA - Life Sciences Subcommittee Minutes, 1988 June (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - National Library of Medicine (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - National Library of Medicine - Draft - Long-Range Plans - Plan 3 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - National Library of Medicine, 1985 November 18-19 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - National Research Initiatives, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
  - National Science Foundation, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - National Science Foundation - National Medal of Science (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - National Science Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - National Science Foundation - Bloch Letter (Agosta) (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - National Science Foundation - Information Technology Program - SBIR (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - National Science Foundation - Science and Technology Centers (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation - Science and Technology Working Group Draft Information (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal-Review (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Chemistry Industry Institute of Toxicology, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 25-26)
  - Chemical Industry Institute of Toxicology (CIIT), 1984-1988 (Box 25, Folder 27-31)
  - Chemical Industry Institute of Toxicology (CIIT), 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 1-21)
  - Universities Research Associates, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 22-24)
  - RU Faculty - William Agosta Research, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - RU Faculty - Kazuko Aoyagi (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - RU Faculty - Dr. Karl E. Anderson (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - RU Faculty - Gwyn Ballard (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - RU Faculty - Francis Barany (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
  - RU Faculty - Beg - Confidential (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - RU Faculty - M.A.R. Beg (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - RU Faculty - Armin Braun (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - RU Faculty - Jan Breslow, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - RU Faculty - Frank Brink (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - RU Faculty - D. M. Carter, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - RU Faculty - Anthony R. Cashmore, 1979-1985 (Box 27, Folder 13-14)
  - RU Faculty - A. Cerami (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - RU Faculty - Michael D. Chafetz (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - RU Faculty - Brian Chait re: Site Visit on March 30, 1988 March 17 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - RU Faculty - K. P. Chang (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - RU Faculty - Johathan Charry (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - RU Faculty - Merill Chase (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - RU Faculty - Nicholas Chiorazzi (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - RU Faculty - Nam Hai Chua (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - RU Faculty - Cole, M. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - RU Faculty - Michael Colgan (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - RU Faculty - Clarence Connelly (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - RU Faculty - Rodney Cool (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - RU Faculty - Paul Cranefield - Grant Application, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - RU Faculty - Timothy J. DeVoogd (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - RU Faculty - Elaine Diacumakos (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - RU Faculty - Thomas J. Dougherty (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - RU Faculty - Adam Drewnowski (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - RU Faculty - Rene Dubos (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - RU Faculty - Barry Dworkin (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - RU Faculty - Ann H. Erickson (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - RU Faculty - Bruce Erickson (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - Mass Spec (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - RU MS Research Resource (Annual Report 1986-1987) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - MS Biotechnology Resource (Annual Report 1985) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - Mass Spec - Annual Report to NIH (Annual Report 1988) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - Grant Application - Application of VG Instrumental (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - Biotech Res Adv. Committee, 1982 February 26 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - Mass Spec Adv. Board - Annual Report, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - RU Faculty - F. Field - Mass Spec - Annual Report, 1980 July (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - RU Faculty - Studies of Specificity-H. Fillit of Anti-Brain Antibodies in Alzheimer's Disease (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - RU Faculty - Jack Fishman (Box 28, Folder 10-13)
  - RU Faculty - John Ford (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - RU Faculty - Stanley D. Fowler (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - RU Faculty - Ernst Friedheim, 1979-1988 (Box 28, Folder 16-25)
  - RU Faculty - Shu Man Fu (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - RU Faculty - Jeffrey Glassberg (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - RU Faculty - James Glimm (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - RU Faculty - Sam Granick (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - RU Faculty - Paul Greengard - Manuscript (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - RU Faculty - Gregory-Vosburgh - Project Proposal (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - RU Faculty - Griffin Am Appdx '78 (Research Proposal), 1978 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - RU Faculty - Joel Grinker (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - RU Faculty - H. K. Hartline (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - RU Faculty - James G. Hirsch (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - RU Faculty - Martin Huh (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - RU Faculty - Rollin D. Hotchkiss (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - RU Faculty - Margeris Jesaitis (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - RU Faculty - Kenneth Johnston - Grant (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - RU Faculty - Dr. Robert Jones (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - RU Faculty - Lois Jovanovic (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - RU Faculty - Mark Kac (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - RU Faculty - Emil Thomas Kaiser (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - RU Faculty - Emil T. Kaiser - Proposal - Peptide Synthesis (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - RU Faculty - Kaiser and Moe (RU-University of Chicago) - Patent Application (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - RU Faculty - Charlotte Kaiser, 1984 March 13 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - RU Faculty - Kaiser - Camile and Henry Dreyfus Grant (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - RU Faculty - A. Kappas (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
  - RU Faculty - Araxie Kilejian (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - RU Faculty - B. Knight (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
  - RU Faculty - Mary Jeanne Kreek, 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - RU Faculty - Henry Kunkel (Box 29, Folder 13-15)
  - RU Faculty - Roberta Lahita (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - RU Faculty - Robert A. Lamb (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - RU Faculty - Rebecca C. Lancefield (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - RU Faculty - Frank R. Landsberger (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - RU Faculty - Fritz Lipmann (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - RU Faculty - David H. Live (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - RU Faculty - Paul Lizardi (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - RU Faculty - William Lowrance, 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 23-26)
  - RU Faculty - Clara J. Lynch (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - RU Faculty - McCarty Talk, 1979 February 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - RU Faculty - Bruce S. McEwen (Box 30, Folder 2-4)
  - RU Faculty - Donald J. McNamara (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - RU Faculty - Maines, M. D. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - RU Faculty - Peter Marler (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - RU Faculty - Alexander Mauro (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - RU Faculty - David Mauzerall II - Grant Application and Research Proposal (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - RU Faculty - Laboratory of Bruce Merrifield (Summary of Work) (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - RU Faculty - George A. Miller (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - RU Faculty - Vincent Monnier (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - RU Faculty - Stanford Moore (Box 30, Folder 13-16)
  - RU Faculty - James J. Murphy (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - RU Faculty - Joseph Nevins (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - RU Faculty - Nadia Noguerira-Codon (Box 30, Folder 19-20)
  - RU Faculty - Ralph Norgren (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - RU Faculty - Geoffrey H. Nowlis (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - RU Faculty - Marie Nyswander (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - RU Faculty - Barry Peterson (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - RU Faculty - Charles Peterson (Box 30, Folder 25-28)
  - RU Faculty - Carl Pfaffman (Box 30, Folder 29-30)
  - RU Faculty - Larissa A. Pohorecky (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - RU Faculty - Elio Presta (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - RU Faculty - Eng-Chong Pua (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - RU Faculty - Thomas C. Rainbow (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - RU Faculty - R. T. Reese (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - RU Faculty - Edward Reich (Box 31, Folder 3-5)
  - RU Faculty - John Riordan (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - RU Faculty - William J. Robbins (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - RU Faculty - Muriel Roger (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - RU Faculty - Peter Ross (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - RU Faculty - Urs Ruthshauser (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - RU Faculty - Anthony I. Sanda (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - RU Faculty - S. Sassa (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - RU Faculty - George Scheele (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - RU Faculty - Andrew Scheid (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - RU Faculty - Wolf-Dieter Schleuning (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - RU Faculty - R. Schoenfeld (Box 31, Folder 16-18)
  - RU Faculty - Morris Schreiber (Box 31, Folder 19-20)
  - RU Faculty - William A. Scott (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - RU Faculty - Robert Shapely (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - RU Faculty - Philip Siekevitz (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - RU Faculty - Samuel Silverstein (Box 31, Folder 24-25)
  - RU Faculty - William Stein (Box 31, Folder 26-28)
  - RU Faculty - Victor Stevens (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - RU Faculty - Sidney Strickland (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - RU Faculty - Jose Sy (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - RU Faculty - Nina F. Tabachnik (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - RU Faculty - William Trager (Box 31, Folder 33-34)
  - RU Faculty - Hung-Sheng Tsao (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - RU Faculty - George Uhlenbeck (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - RU Faculty - Uhrik vs. RU (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - RU Faculty - Jay C. Unkeless (Box 31, Folder 38-39)
  - RU Faculty - Jay Valinsky (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - RU Faculty - Ivo van de Rijn (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - RU Faculty - J. D. Vassalli (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - RU Faculty - Giorgio Vidali (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - RU Faculty - Chia-Gee Wond (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - RU Faculty - Hao Wang (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - RU Faculty - Martin Watterson (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - RU Faculty - Jay Weiss (Box 31, Folder 47-48)
  - RU Faculty - Paul Weiss (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - RU Faculty - Torsten Wiesel (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - RU Faculty - J. Winson (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - RU Faculty - H. Wood, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1982 December 9 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Executive Committee, 1982 October 28 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1982 September 23 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1982 June 10 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1981 October 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Nuclear Project Report, 1981 October (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1981 June 4 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1981 February 5 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 September 18 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - The Business Roundtable (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - March 10 Seminar on Economic Benefits on Environmental Control (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Children and Art (Draft), 1980 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 October 30 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC), 1980 June 5 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 June 5 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 February 14 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC), 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Executive Committee, 1979 September 13 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - The Amicus Journal, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Executive Committee, 1984 February (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC), 1983 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) - Executive Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1-12)
  - Richard Rivlin (Box 33, Folder 13-15)
  - Social Science Research Council (Including: Subcommittee on Science Indicators), 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 16-27)
  - RU Population Biology - Grant Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 28-35)
  - Institute of Medicine, 1978-1982 (Box 34, Folder 1-28)
  - Institute of Medicine, 1976-1980 (Box 35, Folder 1-39)
  - Institute of Medicine, 1978-1981 (Box 36, Folder 1-28)
  - National Research Council - Governing Board Meetings, 1978 January-June (Box 36, Folder 29-31)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - Agenda and Minutes, 1980 May 19-21 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - 1979 Analysis of Construction Data (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - FY 1981-1985, 1980-1985 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - FY 1982-1986, 1981-1986 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report - National Cancer Program (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - Agenda and Minutes, 1980 October 6-8 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Frederick Cancer Research Center (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - A Position Paper (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - FY 1982 Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Cancer Info. Services, 1980 July 1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - Meeting, 1980 May 19 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - Board Meeting, 1980 October 9-11 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - National Cancer Institute - 1979 - NCI Fact Book (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - National Cancer Institute - FY 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Task Force on Environmental Cancer and Heart and Lung Disease (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - IPCP, 1980 October 6-8 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - American Cancer Society - National Conference of Black Americans, 1979 February 15-17 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Pamphlets (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - National Cancer Program - Report of the NCAAB, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - National Cancer Program - NCI - FY 1983 Budget Estimate, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - President's Cancer Panel Meeting - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1981 June 12 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - Success of Cancer Treatment, 1981 October (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - DCCP - Board of Scientific Counselors, 1981 May 28 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Current Clips, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 24-27)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH) - NCI Office of Cancer Communication, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 28-30)
  - International Cancer Research Data Bank - Cancergram, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Clinical Bulletin, 1978, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - CA-A Cancer Journal for Clinicians, 1971, 1975-1980 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - Agenda and Minutes, 1980 May 19-21 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - Frederick Cancer Research Center, 1980 May 19-21 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - DCCP - Board of Scientific Counselors, 1980 September 30 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - National Cancer Program - 1982 Budget Appeal (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Meeting of Board of Scientific Counselors, 1980 September 18-19 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Options for Support of Research - A Position Paper (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Kershner (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board - Agenda, 1980 January 21-23 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board - Index, 1980 January 21-23 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board - Agenda and Minutes, 1980 January 21-23 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - National Cancer Institute - Directors' Research Plan Review, 1980 January 11 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - NIH Bill - Documents Related to S. 988 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Statement of Arthur Uptown before the House Select Committee on Aging, 1979 June (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI), 1979 February-March (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Seer - Cancer Incidence and Morality in the US 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - National Cancer Program - The Strategic Plan, 1973 January (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Transcripts of Proceedings Presidents Cancer Panel Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Scientific Counselors, 1980 March 24-25 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Paper on the NCI Contracting Process, 1980 December 19 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - National Canceer Institute (NCI) - National Prostatic Cancer Project, 1980 October 5 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Preventative Program (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Educational Program (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - National Cancer Institute - Centers and Community Oncology Program (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - DCCP - Board of Scientific Counselors - Minutes, 1980 September 29 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Board of Scientific Counselors Meeting, 1980 October (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Program Plans, 1973-1980 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - National Cancer Advisory Board (NCAB) - 1980 Forward Plan - FY 1982-1984 - Directors' Review Session - Briefing Book (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - Information Procedures (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Presidents Cancer Panel and Div Cancer Treatment - Board of Scientific Couselors, 1981 June 12 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - National Cancer Program Reports (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Devita - NCI (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - NCAB Meeting and PCP, 1980 January 21-23 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Frederick Cancer Research Center - AnnualProgress Report, Vol I, 1978 February-1979 January (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) - General Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) Material - Grant Applications Rejected (Box 39)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) Material - Grant Applications Rejected, 1981 February (Box 39)
  - National Cancer Institute (NCI) Material - Grant Applications Rejected, 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 1-4)
  - Stanford University Genetics - Freshman Seminars, 1973-1976 (Box 40, Folder 5-7)
  - Stanford University Genetics 101, 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 8-11)
  - Stanford University Genetics 201, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University Genetics 101, 1966-1969 (Box 40, Folder 13-16)
  - Stanford University Genetics 201, 1963-1978 (Box 40, Folder 17-28)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee (PSAC)-SIP - Weinberg (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee (PSAC)-SIP - Cardiovascular Pr Welt (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee (PSAC)-SIP - Wigner (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee (PSAC)-SIP - Operations and Schedules (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee (PSAC)-SIP - Stinfo (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee (PSAC)-SIP - DOD (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - President's Panel on Mental Retardation - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Research - President's Panel on Mental Retardation (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - MR Facilitites Act, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - President's Panel on Mental Retardation - Lederberg Notes (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - President's Panel on Mental Retardation (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - President's Panel on Mental Retardation - Amino Acid Conference (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - President's Panel on Mental Retardation - Other Agencies (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - NASA Auxillary Committee - Astronomy, 1961-1962 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - PIP Auxillary Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - NASA - PIP, 1961-1962 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - PIP Correspondence and Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - PIP Meeting 1, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - PIP Meeting 2, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - PIP Meeting 3, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - PIP Meeting 4, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - PIP Meeting 5, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - PIP Meeting 6, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - PIP Meeting 7, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - PIP Meeting 8, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - PIP Meeting 9 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - PIP Meeting 10, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Air Force - IRIS (Space Gov't) (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Intern Activities Cetex 2 (SSB Activities) (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Intern Activities - UN (SSB Activites) (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Moscow, 1961 August (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Intern Activities USSR (Box 41, Folder 32-33)
  - Intern Academy Astronautics (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Space - Gov't Navy and NSF (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Space Sci. Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Space - Indust. Bendix (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Exobiol - Lockheed SC, 1961 November (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Exobiol - Philco (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Exobiology - Varian Associates (Box 41, Folder 40)